Welcome to Oku-Jo's simple tarot reader!
This project is a work in progress, and as my first project without guardrails this might be a bit messy. I hope to keep improving on it as I learn so that I can simplify and refine my coding.
Thank you for reading!

current goal is to add multiple spread options, a full tarot deck (instead of just the major arcana), and user interactions for interpretations.

update: struggling to find a source for a full 78 card tarot deck with up/down explanations that can be scraped (thanks again to Nova for instruction on that), so maybe have user choose which major arcana deck to have drawing made from. found Cyberpunk 2077 major arcana deck, going to try to scrape that now. I recognize this is too much info for a readme, but here we are.


update: learned a bit more about scraping, pretty sure its witchcraft.


update: added cp77 tarot as non-orientation based deck for simpler, less negative reads. committed, going to try to figure out how to get this on github and connect my current workspace with my github account. wish me luck.


update: also scraping is definitely witchcraft, have ordered books on witchcraft.